Finding Aid for the Susan Sontag Papers LSC.0612
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 17: Selected Books from the Library of Susan Sontag, 1783-2001
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1978. (Box 215, Folder 2)
    M.M. Bakhtin. The Formal Method in Literary Scholarship (Baltimore: Johns Hopkins). Signed and annotated by Sontag
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1981. (Box 215, Folder 3)
    M.M. Bakhtin. The Dialogic Imagination (Austin: University of Texas). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Articles inserted
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1930. (Box 215, Folder 4)
    Anton Chekov. Plays (New York: Modern Library). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Articles and program clipping inserted. Upper board detached at spine
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1945. (Box 215, Folder 5)
    Fyodor Dostoyevsky. The Brothers Karamazov (New York: Illustrated Modern Library by Random House). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Paper slip and tickets inserted
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1969. (Box 215, Folder 6)
    Vladimir Markov. Russian Futurism (London: MacGibbon). Book cover back flap detached
  - Film., 1972. (Box 215, Folder 7)
    Stan Brakhage. Lectures (Chicago: Good Lion).
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1975. (Box 216, Folder 1)
    Aleksandr Pushkin. Eugene Onegin, Vol. 1 (New Jersey: Princeton). Signed by Sontag. Article inserted
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1975. (Box 216, Folder 2)
    Aleksandr Pushkin. Eugene Onegin, Vol. 2 (New Jersey: Princeton). Paper slip inserted
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1975. (Box 216, Folder 3)
    Aleksandr Pushkin. Eugene Onegin, Vol. 3 (New Jersey: Princeton). Paper slip inserted
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1975. (Box 216, Folder 4)
    Aleksandr Pushkin. Eugene Onegin, Vol. 4 (New Jersey: Princeton).
  - Film., 1958. (Box 216, Folder 5)
    Michel Laclos. Le Fantastique au Cinema (s.l.: Jean-Jacques Pauvert).
  - Dance, Theater & Music., 1936. (Box 216, Folder 6)
    Vaslav Nijinsky. Diary (New York: Schuster). Articles inserted
  - Dance, Theater & Music., 1930. (Box 216, Folder 7)
    Andre Levinson. Marie Taglioni (London: Beaumont). Paper slips inserted
  - Dance, Theater & Music., 1934. (Box 216, Folder 8)
    Romola Nijinsky. Nijinsky (New York: Schuster). Clipping inserted
  - American Literature., 1925. (Box 217, Folder 1)
    F. Scott Fitzgerald. The Great Gatsby (New York: Scribners). Signed and annotated by Philip Rieff and Sontag. Clippings and articles inserted
  - American Literature., 1937. (Box 217, Folder 2)
    Djuna Barnes. Nightwood (New York: New Directions). Signed by Sontag. Annotated by Philip Rieff and Sontag. Clippings and notepages inserted
  - American Literature., 1935. (Box 217, Folder 3)
    Lincoln Kirstein. Low Ceiling (New York: Putnam). Card inserted (in Box 82, Folder 2)
  - American Literature., 1937. (Box 217, Folder 4)
    Kenneth Burke. Attitudes Toward History (New York: New Republic). Annotated. Clippings inserted
  - American Literature., 1945. (Box 217, Folder 5)
    Gertrude Stein. Wars I Have Seen (New York: Random House). Article inserted
  - American Literature., 1913. (Box 217, Folder 6)
    Edith Wharton. The Custom of the Country (New York: Scribners). Publisher's booklet and Mount pamphlet inserted
  - American Literature., 1950. (Box 217, Folder 7)
    Gertrude Stein. Things As They Are (Vermont: Banyan Press). Signed by Sontag
  - American Literature., 1932. (Box 217, Folder 8)
    Kenneth Burke. Towards a Better Life (New York: Harcourt). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Clipping, articles, Burke death notice, Milo Zwerling birth notice, and paper slip inserted. (Birth notice in Box 142, Folder 32)
  - American Literature., 1941. (Box 217, Folder 9)
    Kenneth Burke. The Philosophy of Literary Form (s.l.: Louisiana State University). Signed and annotated by Philip Rieff and Sontag. Clippings, articles, notepages, and paper slips inserted
  - American Literature., 1956. (Box 218, Folder 1)
    John Berryman. Homage to Mistress Bradstreet (New York: Farrar, Straus & Cudahy). Articles inserted
  - American Literature., 1953. (Box 218, Folder 2)
    Gertrude Stein. Bee Time Vine (New Haven: Yale).
  - American Literature., 1972. (Box 218, Folder 3)
    Gertrude Stein. Matisse Picasso and Gertrude Stein (Barton: Something Else Press). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Poemsheet inserted (moved)
  - American Literature., 1956. (Box 218, Folder 4)
    Gertrude Stein. Stanzas in Meditation (New Haven: Yale).
  - American Literature., 1938. (Box 218, Folder 5)
    Lincoln Kirstein. Blast at Ballet (New York: Marstin Press). Upper cover detached from spine
  - American Literature., 1939. (Box 218, Folder 6)
    Lincoln Kirstein. Ballet Alphabet (New York: Kamin).
  - American Literature., 1965. (Box 218, Folder 7)
    H.P. Lovecraft. Selected Letters, Vol. 1 (Wisconsin: Arkham). Annotated by Sontag. Article inserted
  - American Literature., 1968. (Box 218, Folder 8)
    H.P. Lovecraft. Selected Letters, Vol. 2 (Wisconsin: Arkham). Clipping, article, and paper slip inserted
  - American Literature., 1971. (Box 218, Folder 9)
    H.P. Lovecraft. Selected Letters, Vol. 3 (Wisconsin: Arkham). Annotated by Sontag. Clipping, ticket, and paper slip inserted
  - American Literature., 1969. (Box 219, Folder 1)
    John Cage. Notations (New York: Something Else Press). Inscribed by author to Sontag. Correspondence from Cage and from Cage Trust inserted (now in Box 82, Folder 57)
  - American Literature., 1970. (Box 219, Folder 2)
    Saul Bellow. Mr Sammler's Planet (London: Weidenfeld). Articles inserted
  - American Literature., 1966. (Box 219, Folder 3)
    Paul Goodman. Five Years (New York: Brussel). Annotated by Sontag. Clippings, articles, paper slip, and postcard in Sontag's handwriting inserted
  - American Literature., 1978. (Box 219, Folder 4)
    Paul Goodman. The Break-up of Our Camp (Santa Barbara: Black Sparrow Press). Review slip, clippings, and articles inserted
  - American Literature., 1978. (Box 219, Folder 5)
    Paul Goodman. A Ceremonial (Santa Barbara: Black Sparrow Press). Article inserted
  - American Literature., 1976. (Box 219, Folder 6)
    Elizabeth Bishop. Geography III (New York: Farrar, Straus & Giroux). Articles, clippings, ticket, and author compliments slip inserted
  - American Literature., 1961. (Box 220, Folder 1)
    John Cage. Silence (Connecticut: Wesleyan). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Clippings, article, program, and author compliments slip inserted
  - American Literature., 1978. (Box 220, Folder 2)
    Edgar Allen Poe. Collected Works, Vol. 2 (Cambridge: Belnap). Annotated by Sontag. Notepaper, article, paper slips, and blank postcard inserted
  - American Literature., 1978. (Box 220, Folder 3)
    Edgar Allen Poe. Collected Works, Vol. 3 (Cambridge: Belnap). Paper slips and invitation with sketch on verso inserted. (Invitation moved)
  - American Literature., 1966. (Box 220, Folder 4)
    Gertrude Stein. The Making of Americans (New York: Something Else Press). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Review slip and invitation for Lucinda Childs inserted. (Invitation in Box 83, Folder 24)
  - American Literature., 1997. (Box 220, Folder 5)
    Larry McMurtry and Diana Ossana. Zeke and Ned (New York: Schuster). Inscribed by authors to Sontag
  - Photography., 1973. (Box 221, Folder 1)
    Weegee. Naked City (New York: Da Capo).
  - Art and Architecture., 1965. (Box 221, Folder 2)
    Herbert Marshall, ed. Mayakovsky (New York: Hill and Wang). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Clipping inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1975. (Box 221, Folder 3)
    Ad Reinhardt. Art as Art: Selected Writings (New York: Viking). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Articles, clippings, ticket, and photo inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1966. (Box 221, Folder 4)
    Joseph Cornell (Pasadena: Pasadena Art Museum). Sontag of the exhibit lenders
  - Art and Architecture., 1976. (Box 221, Folder 5)
    Howard Hodgkin: Forty-Five Paintings, 1949-1975 (London: Arts Council). Inscribed by Hodgkin to Sontag. Annotated. Postcard inserted (in Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Art and Architecture., 1969. (Box 221, Folder 6)
    Arp on Arp: Poems, Essays, and Memories (New York: Viking).
  - Art and Architecture., 1960. (Box 221, Folder 7)
    Marcel Duchamp and Richard Hamilton. The Bride Stripped Bare by her Bachelors, Even: a Typographic Version (s.l.: Percy Lund, Humphries).
  - Art and Architecture., 1976. (Box 221, Folder 8)
    K.S. Malevich. The World as Non-Objectivity: Unpublished Writings 1922-25, Vol. 3 (Copenhagen: Borgen). Paper slip inserted
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1967?. (Box 221, Folder 9)
    Film Culture 44, Spring 1967 (New York: Film Culture, Jonas Mekas). Schedule inserted. Fluxus item
  - Photography., 1968. (Box 222, Folder 1)
    Robert Frank. The Americans (New York: Aperture). Signed by Sontag on cover and annotated. Paper slips inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1982. (Box 222, Folder 2)
    Howard Hodgkin: Indian Leaves (London: Petersburg Press). Inscribed by Hodgkin to Sontag. Postcard and address notes inserted (postcard in Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Art and Architecture., 1985. (Box 222, Folder 3)
    Howard Hodgkin: Prints 1977 to 1983 (London: Tate Gallery). Inscribed by Hodgkin to Sontag. Letters and clipping inserted (Hodgkin letter in Box 88, Folder 1; Peattie letter in Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Art and Architecture., 1988. (Box 222, Folder 4)
    Howard Hodgkin (London: Waddington / New York: Knoedler). Inscribed by Hodgkin to Sontag
  - Art and Architecture., 1988. (Box 222, Folder 5)
    Howard Hodgkin (London: Waddington / New York: Knoedler).
  - Art and Architecture., 1990. (Box 222, Folder 6)
    Howard Hodgkin: Petits Formats 1975-1989 (Barcelona: Fundacio Caixa de Pensions). Inscribed by Hodgkin to Sontag
  - Art and Architecture., 1990. (Box 222, Folder 7)
    Wilfried Dickhoff. Howard Hodgkin (New York: Knoedler).
  - Art and Architecture., 1998. (Box 222, Folder 8)
    Howard Hodgkin (New York: Gagosian Gallery). Notecard, exhibit ephemera, and articles inserted. (Notecard in Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Art and Architecture., 1986. (Box 222, Folder 9)
    Howard Hodgkin (New York: Knoedler). Exhibit postcard inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1991. (Box 222, Folder 10)
    Howard Hodgkin: Hand Coloured Prints 1986-1991 (London: Waddington Graphics). Inscribed by Hodgkin to Sontag
  - Art and Architecture., 1990. (Box 222, Folder 11)
    Wilfried Dickhoff. Howard Hodgkin (Koln: Michael Werner). Inscribed by Hodgkin to Sontag
  - Photography., 1972. (Box 223, Folder 1)
    Gordon Hendricks. The Photographs of Thomas Eakins (New York: Grossman). Paper slips, postcard, and articles inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1929?. (Box 223, Folder 2)
    L'Art International d'Aujourd'hui, Vol. 11: Objets d'Art; Prsent par Pierre Legrain (Paris: Charles Moreau). Loose plates in portfolio
  - Art and Architecture., 1929?. (Box 223, Folder 3)
    L'Art International d'Aujourd'hui, Vol. 17: Reliures; Prsent par Rose Adler (Paris: Charles Moreau). Loose plates in portfolio
  - Art and Architecture., 1988. (Box 224, Folder 1)
    Prag um 1600: Kunst und Kultur am Hofe Rudolfs II (Freren: Luca). Articles inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1988. (Box 224, Folder 2)
    Prag um 1600: Kunst und Kultur am Hofe Rudolfs II, 2. Band (Freren: Luca). Clippings inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1988. (Box 224, Folder 3)
    Prag um 1600: Beitrage zur Kunst und Kultur am Hofe Rudolfs II (Freren: Luca).
  - Art and Architecture., 1993. (Box 224, Folder 4)
    Howard Hodgkin (London: Anthony d'Offay Gallery). Exhibit pamphlet inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1984. (Box 224, Folder 5)
    Howard Hodgkin: Forty Paintings (London: Trefoil Books). Annotated by Sontag. Card, exhibit ephemera, articles, and bio inserted. (Card in Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Art and Architecture., 1994. (Box 224, Folder 6)
    Andrew Graham-Dixon. Howard Hodgkin (London: Thames and Hudson). Annotated by Sontag and inscribed to Sontag by Hodgkin. Postcard, event program, articles, bio, and paper slips inserted. (Postcard in Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Dance, Theater & Music., 1975. (Box 225, Folder 1)
    Lincoln Kirstein. Nijinsky Dancing (New York: Knopf). Pamphlet inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1989. (Box 225, Folder 2)
    Andy Goldsworthy. Touching North (London: Fabian Carlsson). Exhibit postcards inserted
  - Photography., 1998. (Box 225, Folder 3)
    Andreas Gursky. Fotografien, 1994-1998 (Wolfsburg: Kunstmuseum Wolfsburg). Signed by artist. Prospectus inserted
  - Photography., 1995. (Box 225, Folder 4)
    Bernd and Hilla Becher. Industrial Facades (Cambridge: MIT). Article, clipping, and postcards inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1967. (Box 226, Folder 1)
    Anthony Blunt. Nicholas Poussin: Text / Nicholas Poussin: Plates (New York: Pantheon). Two volumes in slipcase
  - Art and Architecture., 1929?. (Box 227, Folder 1)
    L'Art International d'Aujourd'hui, Vol. 4: Terrasses et Jardins; Prsent par Andr Lurcat (Paris: Charles Moreau). Loose plates in portfolio
  - Art and Architecture., 1929?. (Box 227, Folder 2)
    L'Art International d'Aujourd'hui, Vol. 8: Boutiques et Magasins; Prsent par Ren-Herbst (Paris: Charles Moreau). Loose plates, some color printed, in portfolio
  - Art and Architecture., 1993. (Box 227, Folder 3)
    Lucio Fino. Vesuvio e Campi Flegrei (Napoli: Grimaldi). In slipcase
  - Art and Architecture., 1936. (Box 227, Folder 4)
    Nils G. Wollin. Desprez I Sverige (Stockholm: P.A. Norstedt & Soner). Notepaper inserted. In clamshell box
  - Art and Architecture., 1929?. (Box 228, Folder 1)
    L'Art International d'Aujourd'hui, Vol. 7: Meubles; Prsent par Pierre Chareau (Paris: Charles Moreau). Loose plates, some color printed, in portfolio
  - Art and Architecture., 1929?. (Box 228, Folder 2)
    L'Art International d'Aujourd'hui, Vol. 6: Intrieurs; Prsent par Francis Jourdain (Paris: Charles Moreau). Loose plates, some color printed, in portfolio
  - Art and Architecture., 1929?. (Box 228, Folder 3)
    L'Art International d'Aujourd'hui, Vol. 5: Dtails d'Architecture Intrieure; Prsent par A. Novi (Paris: Charles Moreau). Loose plates in portfolio
  - Art and Architecture., no date. (Box 229, Folder 1)
    Otto Benesch. Egon Schiele as a Draughtsman (Vienna: State Printing Office of Vienna). Loose prints in jacket
  - Art and Architecture., 1933. (Box 229, Folder 2)
    Nils G. Wollin. Gravures Originales de Desprez (Malmo: John Kroon). In clamshell box
  - Art and Architecture., 1979. (Box 230, Folder 1)
    Diane DeGrazia Bohlin. Prints and Related Drawings by the Carracci Family (Bloomington: Indiana University).
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1983. (Box 230, Folder 2)
    Prsences Polonaises (Paris: Centre Georges Pompidou). Annotated. Articles and notes inserted
  - Russian and Eastern European Literature., 1979. (Box 230, Folder 3)
    Art et Posie Russes (Paris: Centre Georges Pompidou). Annotated
  - Art and Architecture., 1985. (Box 231, Folder 1)
    The Royal Pictures Gallery: Mauritshuis (Amsterdam: Meulenhoff / Landshoff). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Picture, clipping and exhibit pamphlet inserted
  - Photography., 1971. (Box 231, Folder 2)
    Paul Strand: a Retrospective Monograph, the Years 1950-1968 (New York: Aperture). Annotated
  - Photography., 1990. (Box 232, Folder 1)
    Richard Misrach. Bravo 20 (Baltimore: Johns Hopkins). Exhibit ephemera, clipping, and postcard inserted. (Postcard in Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Art and Architecture., 1993. (Box 232, Folder 2)
    Joseph Leo Koerner. The Moment of Self-Portraiture in German Renaissance Art (Chicago: University of Chicago). Article and clipping inserted.
  - Photography., 1973. (Box 232, Folder 3)
    August Sander. Men Without Masks (Connecticut: New York Greenwich Society). Annotated. In slipcase
  - Art and Architecture., 1974. (Box 232, Folder 4)
    Dore Ashton. A Joseph Cornell Album (New York: Viking). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Exhibit ephemera, article, and notes inserted
  - Photography., 1981. (Box 233, Folder 1)
    Paul Outerbridge: a Singular Aesthetic (Santa Barbara, CA: Arabesques Books). Inscribed to Annie Leibovitz by editor? Articles and blank postcard laid in
  - Photography., 1981. (Box 233, Folder 2)
    Man Ray: Photographe (Paris: Philippe Sers). Articles, clippings, exhibit checklist, and letter (letter in Box 141, Folder 42)
  - Photography., 1977. (Box 233, Folder 3)
    Bernd und Hilla Becher. Fachwerkhauser (Munchen: Schirmer / Mosel). Clipping and gallery pamphlets inserted
  - Photography., 1989. (Box 233, Folder 4)
    Bernd and Hilla Becher. Water Towers (Cambridge: MIT). Signed and annotated by Sontag. Clipping, article, postcard, and exhibit ephemera inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1970. (Box 234, Folder 1)
    J.-B. de la Faille. The Works of Vincent van Gogh (New York: William Morrow). Clippings and articles inserted
  - Photography., 1973. (Box 235, Folder 1)
    Edward Weston. Daybooks, I: Mexico (New York: Aperture). Annotated. Articles, clippings, exhibit pamphlet, and book order slip inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1958?. (Box 235, Folder 2)
    The Complete Letters of Vincent van Gogh, Vol. 1 (Connecticut: New York Graphic Society). Articles and bookmark inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1958?. (Box 235, Folder 3)
    The Complete Letters of Vincent van Gogh, Vol. 2 (Connecticut: New York Graphic Society).
  - Art and Architecture., 1958?. (Box 235, Folder 4)
    The Complete Letters of Vincent van Gogh, Vol. 3 (Connecticut: New York Graphic Society).
  - Photography., 1973. (Box 235, Folder 5)
    Edward Weston. Daybooks, II: California (New York: Aperture). Annotated. Paper slip, clipping, and exhibit pamphlet inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1982. (Box 236, Folder 1)
    Hammacher. Van Gogh: a Documentary Biography (New York: Macmillan). Annotated. Clippings and postcards inserted. (One postcard in Box 145, Folder 34)
  - Art and Architecture., 1975. (Box 236, Folder 2)
    Anthony Blunt. Neapolitan Baroque and Rococo Architecture (London: Zwemmer). Article inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1978. (Box 236, Folder 3)
    Paris-Berlin: 1900-1933 (Paris: Centre Georges Pompidou). Annotated. Clippings, paper slips, exhibit layout with notes, and articles
  - Photography., 1991. (Box 236, Folder 4)
    Horst: Sixty Years of Photgraphy (New York: Rizzoli). Signed by Horst. Articles inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1960. (Box 237, Folder 1)
    Francis Picabia. 391 (Paris: Terrain Vague). Signed by Sontag
  - Art and Architecture., 1982. (Box 237, Folder 2)
    Herbert Bayer: das Kunstlerische Werk, 1918-1938 (Berlin: Mann). Clipping inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1969. (Box 237, Folder 3)
    Mario Praz. On Neoclassicism (Evanston: Northwestern University). Annotated. Articles and paper slips inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1993. (Box 237, Folder 4)
    Gerard Richter, Vols. 1-3 (Bonn: Kunst- und Ausstellungshalle der Bundesrepublik Deutschland). Three volumes in slipcase
  - Art and Architecture., 1974. (Box 238, Folder 1)
    Rudolf Wittkower. Gothic vs. Classic (New York: George Braziller). Article inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1976. (Box 238, Folder 2)
    Joseph Cornell. Portfolio-Catalogue (New York: Castelli Gallery/Feigen Comapny/Corcoran Gallery). Loose sheets, photo, and tribute letters in portfolio with left and right pockets. Clippings inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1966. (Box 238, Folder 3)
    Otto Kallir. Egon Schiele: Oeuvre Catalogue of the Paintings (New York: Crown). In slipcase
  - Photography., 2001. (Box 239, Folder 1)
    Bernd and Hilla Becher. Framework Houses (Cambridge: MIT).
  - Art and Architecture., 1943. (Box 239, Folder 2)
    Camille Pisarro. Letters to his Son Lucien (New York: Pantheon).
  - Photography., 1990. (Box 239, Folder 3)
    Bernd und Hilla Becher. Hochofen (Munchen: Schirmer / Mosel). Article, postcard, checklist inserted
  - Photography., 1997. (Box 239, Folder 4)
    Bernd and Hilla Becher. Mineheads (Cambridge: MIT).
  - Photography., 1990. (Box 239, Folder 5)
    Bernd and Hilla Becher. Tipologie (Munchen: Schirmer / Mosel).
  - Art and Architecture., 1990. (Box 240, Folder 1)
    Jean Prouv: Constructeur (Paris: Centre Georges Pompidou). Annotated. Paper slip inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1991. (Box 240, Folder 2)
    Max Ernst: das Rendezvous der Freunde (Koln: Museum Ludwig). Clipping inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1976. (Box 240, Folder 3)
    Francis Picabia (Paris: Centre Georges Pompidou). Signed by Sontag
  - Photography., 1995. (Box 240, Folder 4)
    Thomas Kellein. Hiroshi Sugimoto: Time Exposed (London: Thames and Hudson).
  - Photography., 1985. (Box 240, Folder 5)
    Rosalind Krauss and Jane Livingston. L'Amour Fou (New York: Abbeville). Annotated by Sontag. Paper slips and articles inserted
  - Photography., 1986. (Box 241, Folder 1)
    Nan Goldin. The Ballad of Sexual Dependency (New York: Aperture). Articles and exhibit ephemera inserted
  - Photography., 1989. (Box 241, Folder 2)
    Walker Evans. Havana (New York: Pantheon). Clipping and exhibit postcard inserted
  - Photography., 1940. (Box 241, Folder 3)
    Paul Outerbridge. Photographing in Color (New York: Random House). Note card and postcard inserted. Spine tearing at top
  - Photography., 1983. (Box 241, Folder 4)
    Robert Mapplethorpe. Lady Lisa Lyon (New York: Viking). Inscribed by Mapplethorpe to Sontag. Articles and clippings inserted
  - Photography., 1990. (Box 241, Folder 5)
    Bruce Weber. Bear Pond (s.l.: Bullfinch).
  - Photography., 1976. (Box 241, Folder 6)
    Richard Avedon. Portraits (New York: Farrar, Straus & Giroux). Inscribed by Avedon to Sontag. Clippings, articles, photo inserted
  - Photography., 1972. (Box 242, Folder 1)
    Diane Arbus (New York: Aperture). Annotated by Sontag. Prints, articles, clippings, and exhibit ephemera inserted
  - Photography., 1974. (Box 242, Folder 2)
    Andr Kertsz. J'Aime Paris (New York: Grossman).
  - Photography., 1993. (Box 242, Folder 3)
    Annie Leibovitz. Photographs (New York: Pantheon / Rolling Stone Press). Postcard and clipping inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1951. (Box 242, Folder 4)
    The Dada Painters and Poets: an Anthology (New York: Wittenborn Schultz). Signed by Sontag. Article and paper slips inserted. Cover damaged. Pages slightly warped
  - Art and Architecture., 1968. (Box 242, Folder 5)
    El Lissitzky: Life, Letters, Text (London: Thames and Hudson). Clipping inserted
  - Art and Architecture., 1982. (Box 243, Folder 1)
    Benedetto Gravagnuolo. Adolf Loos: Theory and Works (New York: Rizzoli). Clippings, receipt, and bookmark with message included
  - Photography., 1983. (Box 243, Folder 2)
    The Work of Atget, Vol. 3 (New York: Museum of Modern Art). Clippings, exhibit ephemera, and articles inserted
  - Photography., 1985. (Box 243, Folder 3)
    The Work of Atget, Vol. 4 (New York: Museum of Modern Art).
  - Photography., 1993. (Box 244, Folder 1)
    Bernd and Hilla Becher. Gas Tanks (Cambridge: MIT). Exhibit flyer inserted
  - Photography., 1981. (Box 244, Folder 2)
    The Work of Atget, Vol. 1 (New York: Museum of Modern Art).
  - Photography., 1982. (Box 244, Folder 3)
    The Work of Atget, Vol. 2 (New York: Museum of Modern Art). Article and letter in between Vol. 2 and Vol. 1. (Letter in Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Art and Architecture., 1983. (Box 245, Folder 1)
    Yves Klein (Paris: Centre Georges Pompidou). Articles, clippings, exhibit ephemera, and postcard inserted. (Postcard in Box 145, Folder 34)
  - Photography., 1970. (Box 245, Folder 2)
    E.J. Bellocq: Storyvills Portraits (New York: Museum of Modern Art). Article, gallery pamphlet, and print control strips inserted